♫ In the not too distant future
♫ Next Sunday, AD
♫ There was a guy named Joel
♫ Not too different from you or me
♫ He worked at Gizmonic Institute
♫ Just another face in a red jumpsuit
♫ He did a good job cleaning up the place
♫ But his bosses didn't like him
♫ So they shot him into space
♫ We'll send him cheesy
movies, the worst we can find
♫ La, la, la
♫ He'll have to sit and watch them all
♫ Then we'll monitor his mind
♫ La, la, la
♫ Now keep in mind Joel can't control
♫ Where the movies begin or end
♫ La, la, la
♫ Because he used those special parts
♫ To make his robot friends
♫ Robot roll call
♫ Cambot, pan left
♫ Gypsy, hi, girl
♫ Tom Servo, what a cool guy
♫ Crow, what a wise-cracker
♫ You're wondering how
he eats and breathes
♫ And other science facts
♫ La, la, la
♫ Then repeat to yourself it's just a show
♫ I should really just relax
♫ For Mystery Science Theater 3000 ♫
- [Servo] A one, a two,
we know what to do.
♫ We're the Satellite of Love
♫ Oh, the Satellite of Love
♫ In spite of our
situation, we're just fine
♫ So, forget about rejoicing
♫ And wait for Magic Voice
♫ It's 30 seconds to
commercial sign, we-hoo
♫ So a couple of dumpy overlords
have shot us into space
♫ We'll take this stupid
experiment and jam it in their face
♫ Crow, Gypsy, Servo, Joel
♫ Stories, fun toys
♫ We don't care, don't despair
♫ We're not wearin' our underwear
♫ We're on the Satellite of Love
♫ Warriors of the world ♫
- By Marx!
(upbeat pop music)
- Alright, the best
thing about performing --
- Yeah, right there, right there.
Ah.
- Is having the rockin'
wrap party afterwards.
(cheering)
- Yeah, alright.
- Alright, and then when
you're done with him, Tom,
it's time for my back
rub, and then we sauna.
(laughs)
- Yeah, yeah, I'll give you a back rub,
as soon as I'm done with Crow here.
- No, I'll give you both a back rub
when Tommy's done with me.
- Okay.
- I'm going to put on Bette
Midler so we can dance.
- Yeah!
- [Crow] Aw, great idea.
Hey, and then we can all
go down to the piano bar
at Nuys, and sing show tunes!
(cheering)
- Oh, the evil impresarios
are calling, you guys.
- Well, Weenie-Buns, I think we've
really outdone ourselves this time.
Not only have we found a movie
that'll make your toes curl,
but your shoes and socks, as well.
(laughs)
- Yeah, I thought the
composting toilet had backed up.
As it turns out, it's
this week's experiment.
(laughs)
- [Both] Woo!
- Hey, Joel?
- But first, let's have at
that invention exchange, hmm?
- Ah, um, I'll be right back.
- Well, should we show 'em ours?
- Oh, yeah, good plan.
Hey, sirs, we have our
own invention this time.
Cambot, move it in here --
- Right here in my hand, Cambot.
You see it?
- See?
- You see, it's a new long
distance telephone transducer,
that operates at seven ohms,
and nominal temperature
range of zero to 50 degrees, Celsius.
- Yeah, it's a marked improvement
over the old configuration,
that often required
over 25 seconds to connect
transcontinental signals.
It does so at half the cost.
- And it's completely solid state.
- Mm-hmm.
- You see, the chip
sees a telephone signal
as a series of ones and
zeroes, which are the --
- Hey, guys, I found out.
Here's the invention exchange,
it's called the big head.
- Joel, we did the big head already.
- Really?
- Yep, uh-huh.
- [Crow] Uh-huh.
- Yes, well, let's press on, dingle-berry.
Our --
- Hey, who's that guy with the big head?
- Cork it, Larry.
Our experiment this week is in honor
of your horribly, stinky film.
We all remember and love the
antics of comedian Joe Besser,
on the old Abbott and Costello Show.
Well, we can relive those
moments with my new stinky bomb.
- Yes, now you can turn
any friend into that
lovable buffoon, who
was a lisping man-child,
long before it became fashionable.
- I think it would go something like this.
(explosion)
- Oh!
- Elegant, isn't it?
Yes, yes.
- I'll harm you.
(thud)
- Well, Joel, it's time for me
to send you your own stink bomb.
This film makes The Unearthly
look like Citizen Kane.
- I'll give you such a pinch, oh.
- Ow!
- It's called The Castle of Fu Manchu.
(thud)
- Take a tall drink of gray water, Joel.
It'll help you get in the mood.
Send him the film.
- What if I don't want to.
(cries)
I don't want, ow!
(thud)
Oh, I'll harm you!
(buzzing)
- Movie time, movie time!
I didn't know we had
done that one already.
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Servo] Yeah, we sure,
oh, look, it's filmed in Oakland.
- [Crow] Hey.
- [Joel] Oh, what a wonderful, lenten sky.
- [Voiceover] This is Fu Manchu.
- And you're not.
- [Voiceover] Once again,
the world is at my mercy.
- [Servo] Mercy!
(growls)
- [Voiceover] I have conquered,
not only the mysteries
of the continent, but
now, of the oceans, too.
- [Servo] And the ancient
secret of ventriloquism,
now you can too!
- [Voiceover] In the tropical
waters of the South Atlantic,
my hand stretches out
to turn water into ice.
- Oh, he's a refrigerator.
- [Voiceover] And transform safety,
into the deadliest peril.
- [Joel] Kind of like a Corvair, huh?
- [Voiceover] In a few moments,
the proof of my mastery will be complete.
- [Servo] But first, this
word from Maxwell House.
(ragtime music)
- [Joel] Oh, they stole
this from a Titanic movie.
Look.
- O, 73.
- [Servo] We use children
to grind our hops.
- [Man] Number three, yet?
- [Joel] Three cherries!
- [Servo] I wonder what this is.
It's a Chinese personal computer.
(laughs)
- [Joel] Well said.
- [Servo] Go portable.
- They must use ninja dolphin temps.
- There's no danger of overload.
- [Joel] I didn't ask.
- One of the staff in the
powerhouse make a mistake,
generate more energy than we need.
- I'm mixing my album, leave me alone.
- Installed his safety lock.
- [Servo] Oh, he's cool Fu Mo-Gee.
(mimicking hip hop beat)
- [Joel] Oh, he's wearing
David Byrne's big suit.
Check it out.
- [Servo] Oh, how about that?
- [Crow] Big pajamas.
- When this lever reaches
the bottom of the groove,
we are at safety maximum.
- [Servo] Then let your
foot off the clutch.
- Take the lever, and move it
down into the second groove,
before the auxiliary
channels will feed in.
- [Servo] Auxiliary?
(buzz)
(gasps)
- He's flat-lining!
- [Fu Manchu] Phase two, coming in now.
- [Servo] Any time, come on in.
Phase two, ladies and gentlemen.
- [Joel] Jiggle the plug,
sometimes you gotta kick it.
(water crashing)
- The signal isn't getting through.
- [Servo] Hmm.
- [Fu Manchu] Strengthen the signal.
- No!
- Do as I say!
Strengthen it!
- [Servo] Listen, my name
is on your check, buddy.
- [Fu Manchu] More!
- [Joel] Oh, it's a quad system.
- We still have the safety lock.
- Hey, don't get your
tie stuck in that thing.
- [Joel] That's the biggest
rock tumbler I have ever seen.
- [Servo] Big wheel, keep on turnin'.
(mimics fog horn)
- Do we have to see this?
- No, we cannot!
- Do it, do it!
- No, no, no!
- [Servo] Dammit, push the lever!
- I won't do it.
- [Servo] Will you push the lever?
- I won't do it!
- [Servo] It's Witness, all of a sudden.
(laughs)
- Lin Tang, slide that lever over.
Slide it over and hold it!
- [Joel] That girl!
- [Servo] Like this?
- Oh, yes, oh, yes.
Girth.
(mimics fog horn)
(gun shot)
- [Servo] Oh, she exploded.
Oh.
- [Crow] Oh.
- [Servo] Thought she'd --
(suspenseful music)
- [Joel] Looks like my freezer.
(yells)
- [Servo] Ooh, gotta do
something about that.
- [Joel] Deploy the
bread, deploy the bread.
Wonder bread.
- Lucy must be around here somewhere.
(laughs)
Ah, Ricky, I hit an iceberg.
Ah.
- [Joel] Call it quits.
That pretty much screws
up the shuffleboard.
Come on.
- [Servo] Hey, the water
got warmer in here.
- Thank you, Wang, that'll be all.
- [Joel] Nose to the grindstone, you.
- [Servo] Oh, somebody wet the bed.
(laughs)
- So, I called down the desk clerk.
I said, "I had a leak in the sink".
He said, "Go ahead, the
customer's always right."
(laughs)
- [Joel] Like Dave.
(yells)
(mimicking circus music)
- [Servo] Uh-oh.
- Women, children, spacemen, Indians,
and sort of idealized representations
of 16th century Flemish merchants first!
(screams)
- [Joel] Kathy Lee, no!
- [Servo] Boy, these people
really know how to party.
Woo!
It's a Carnival cruise.
(laughs)
- [Voiceover] In a few
moments, the entire ship
will have vanished beneath
the ocean's surface.
- [Servo] Bing, bing, bing.
- This is the destiny of Fu Manchu.
- [Servo] And you are there.
- And now back to our Channel Nine movie,
the Poseidon Adventure.
(yelling)
(mimicking singing underwater)
- [Joel] Ooh.
(suspenseful music)
- [All] Ah!
Ooh!
(screams)
- [Crow] Ah!
(mimics talking underwater)
(screaming)
- [Joel] Sliders.
(bang)
(thud)
- [Crow] Huh?
- [Servo] Oh, Gilligan.
Oh.
(mimics talking underwater)
- [Fu Manchu] Lin Tang, follow me.
- [Servo] Come, let's have a quick one.
Cocktail.
Ah, wee!
(thud)
- [Joel] Waiter, waiter.
We'll have the Buddha Delight, pronto.
Yeah, mm-hmm.
- [Servo] Lousy service.
♫ There has got to be an ever-after ♫
(laughs)
And there she goes.
Yay!
- Well, that made no sense.
- [Servo] Epilogue.
Well, Rocky, it turns out that Jimmy
was hiding in the Camaro.
- [Joel] Now, it's Adventures In Paradise.
♫ Fu Manchu
♫ A real bad man with a plan, that's Fu
♫ He's the clown in the robe
♫ Stands about seven foot, two
- [Joel] I'll have the number
six, the Christopher Lee.
It comes with egg roll, you know?
- [Servo] Ooh.
- [Joel] Yes?
- [Servo] Yeah?
- [Joel] In what?
- Oh.
- [Servo] Oh, Rohmer, he's
in A Dead Man At Maude's,
falling on the beach.
- [Joel] No, that's Eric Rohmer.
- [Servo] Oh.
- Castle of Fu Manchu, where you eat
square hamburgers with chopsticks.
- [Servo] Huh?
- [Joel] You know, they
should've stuck Martin up there
with Crawford, and everyone
would have two names.
- [Servo] Hey, look!
It's Howard and Marion from
Happy Days, Richie's parents.
♫ Taboo, taboo
- Richard Greene is Nayland Smith.
Ba-dum-bum-bum.
- [Joel] Role provided by Manuel Merino.
♫ Fu Manchu
- [Servo] Oh, Camilleri.
I love it with a light horseradish sauce.
- [Joel] It's calamari.
- [Servo] Oh, you're right.
Always make that mistake.
♫ I'm bored, I'm bored
with these credits already
(laughs)
- Oh, come on.
We can't keep making fun of
the names, get on with it!
- [Joel] Titles by Peter Max.
Are these the same towers or?
Oh, look, even the towers
got their own credits.
(laughs)
♫ Produced by Harry Allan Towers
♫ Harry Allan Towers
♫ Harry Allen Towers ♫
(upbeat pop music)
Last week on Grizzly Adams.
(birds chirping)
- [Servo] Hey, it's Gadabout
Gaddis, the flying fisherman.
- Before Babe Winkleman,
there was Gadabout Gaddis.
- [Fishing Man] I've got a bite!
- [Servo] Oh, cripes.
You need a lazy Ike on
that there, I think.
- [Fishing Man] I've landed
a real monster, this time.
- [Man] This isn't Loch Ness, Petrie.
You want a hand?
- No, I can manage.
This a tiny shrimp.
- [Joel] Good job.
You caught a tree with that little fish.
That's not bad.
- [Man] Bravo, Petrie!
- [Petrie] Be quiet.
Yes, alright, I must say this is --
- [Servo] It's amazing
how these British blend in
with their natural
environments, isn't it now?
- After landing that
monster, you must be hungry.
Let's open the picnic basket.
- [Joel] Oh, dad, your medication.
Did you take the pills from
Monday's little container?
- [Servo] Woo!
Look at this guy.
Who's dressin' him today?
(laughs)
- Hello, what's this?
- Probably fish, ham, and sandwiches.
(mumbles)
- Iceberg In The Tropics?
- What do you say?
- Listen, liner strikes
iceberg, hundreds drown.
- Good God, where?
- [Crow] In the water.
- In the Caribbean.
Icebergs in the Caribbean.
Paper's a week old.
- [Joel] And so is this sandwich.
- [Man] Nayland Smith!
Petrie!
- [All] Dish.
- Hello.
- [Petrie] Hello, Curt.
- [Servo] Come here, Petrie, old man.
He's a lovely chap, (mumbles)
- [Nayland] Hello, Kessler,
what brings you here?
- My bicycle.
(laughs)
- [Curt] Looks rather urgent.
♫ Harry and the kids are dead
♫ Harry and the kids are ♫
I thought I'd try and find
you, before I got the thing.
- [Nayland] Thank you, Curt.
It was very kind of you to come.
- [Joel] Well, I didn't mean to,
but the new seat covers --
- [Servo] Joel, no!
- [Kessler] Fish aren't
biting well today, Petrie, uh?
- Everybody can't be an Isaac Walton.
- [Crow] Don't wave your
little sizzler at me, dad.
- Not yet.
(laughs)
- Somebody may be joining
you on the London train.
- I'm here for the old gringo audition.
- [Servo] Sounds like he had a little shot
of testosterone there.
(laughs)
- Well, we've got another week yet!
- Holidays are over, Petrie.
This is from the Home Secretary.
We've been ordered back to London at once.
- [Servo] Oh, well,
that's our Home Secretary.
(laughs)
- [Joel] Hey, now, it's
Thomas the Tank Engine, man.
- [Servo] This is symbolic
of their return to London.
(laughs)
(clears throat)
- [Joel] Meanwhile, in
downtown Ames, Iowa.
- [Servo] In Chicago, I'm
Grant Park, in Lakeshore Drive.
The Field Museum.
(beeping)
- [Joel] Our lunch today will
be toasted cheese sandwiches,
tomato soup, turkey
tidbits, and tater tots.
- [Voiceover] Stand by for an
important message from Fu Manchu.
- [Joel] Mm-hmm.
- [Man] How long have these messages
been coming in, Sir Robert?
- [Crow] Well, that's a rather
personal question, isn't it?
- Over the past 24 hours.
At first, we didn't take them
very seriously, but now --
- Is the wave length being monitored?
- Yes, of course.
(mimics explosion)
- [Servo] Mm, his finger went off.
- Bastard's speaking
through our omelet pan!
(gasps)
- [Voiceover] This is Fu Manchu.
- [Servo] And I'm an alcoholic.
- [Joel] Hi, Fu!
- [Voiceover] In the Caribbean Sea --
I gave a demonstration of the new --
- [Servo] What?
- [Voiceover] And destructive
weapon that I possess.
- [Crow] Hello?
Hey, lights please!
- [Joel] You know, it
kind of looks like a Nova
special on conception, doesn't it?
- [Servo] Yeah.
- [Joel] Focus!
- [Servo] Somethin'.
We're green!
They're green.
Hmm?
Not again.
- If disaster is to be avoided,
I shall insist on complete cooperation.
I shall give no further warning,
but unless the heads of
state of the major powers --
- [Joel] Looks like Fu
shops at Ethan Allen.
(laughs)
- [Servo] Tasteful.
- [Voiceover] In 14 days
from now, I shall strike.
- [Servo] Does that start today?
Is that 14 business days,
or would that be weekdays?
- [Joel] Ah, Fu, this
is the River Boat Queen.
We'll catch you on the flip flop.
Catch you later, good buddy.
HT at 10 four.
- Fu Manchu hasn't lost his cunning.
He's used at least four
transmitters, impossible to trace.
He's threatened mankind with obliteration.
It sounded almost biblical.
- [Man] That's one book in which
you won't find Fu Manchu's name.
- [Crow] Quite.
- I was thinking of the flood.
In some way, Fu Manchu's new weapon
involves water and its temperature.
- Staring contest on the left.
Check it out.
- [Servo] You blinked.
- In a spot where he could control
great quantities of water.
Panama, Gibraltar, Suez.
- [Servo] Ruby Falls.
- Or even Istanbul.
- [Servo] Wisconsin Dells?
The Opa Dells.
- Ooh, let's go there now.
- [Joel] Oh, sure.
Just barge right into Istanbul.
- [Crow] No!
- [Servo] Oh, that's terrible!.
- [Joel] Well, it's not Constantinople.
- [Crow] Uh-uh.
♫ Istanbul is Constantinople
♫ Istanbul ♫
(seagulls chirping)
♫ Hey, Mr. Armstein ♫
- [Joel] Rula Lenska as the
Turkish lieutenant's woman.
(laughs)
- Gee, I don't recognize him,
but the fez is familiar.
(mimics rim shot)
- [Servo] Either I'm weird,
or that guy's really hot.
- Oh, it's Annie Hall.
- [Joel] Bet he's smokin' a Camel, huh?
(laughs)
- [Servo] Turkish and domestic blend.
(ominous jazz music)
- It's like a meeting
of the Shriner Mafia.
- [Servo] Do you like this pole?
- This water splits out.
- [Crow] What?
- The search of the sun.
- I have been sent by Omar Pasha --
- [Joel] There goes a spooky sub.
- Good, we have no time to waste.
- Yeah, whatever.
- [Servo] Hey, look,
Pac-Man's got his own flag.
- [Joel] Oh.
- We're just two ships
passing in the, uh, day.
(laughs)
(humming)
- [Joel] Catalina Caper, right?
Are you following me?
Quit following me.
(ominous music)
Heel, I don't want you following me.
- All we are is dust in the wind, man.
- [Joel] That's so true.
♫ I have often walked
down this road before ♫
- [Servo] Well, you see.
The theory is you're harder to see,
when you sneak around like that.
(bubbling)
- Next, we travel to
Istanbul with Robert Goulet,
as he hooks up with that non-co-sheggie.
- [Joel] Janie?
- Master, I have brought the lady.
- Oh, wow, I'm so high.
- [Servo] Excuse me, while I kiss the sky.
- Persistent lady.
Greetings.
Sit down please.
- [Servo] I am sitting down.
- You have received my message?
- What have you to sell me?
- Opium.
- [Servo] Hmm.
- I have enough opium.
- [Crow] How about Chanel No 5?
- To control the trade
of half of the world.
- You are starting to interest me.
- You are one of the few that
passed the governor's castle.
- [Servo] The proud, the Marines.
- Yes?
- The governor's castle
contains the biggest reserve
of opium in the East, but the --
- [Joel] What are we waiting for then?
Road trip, dude.
Whoa.
- [Crow] Woo!
- I'm interested.
- If you agree, we will share the opium.
- [Crow] With her and her roommates.
- Explain to me your plans.
- [Voiceover] You will send your men
up the river Bosphorus --
- [Servo] We gotta go, guys.
Oh, this movie's bad.
- [Voiceover] Leaving the way clear,
for me and my men, to approach on feet.
(cries)
- Oh, are we on?
(clears throat)
The Miss Saigon Syndrome, an
editorial by Crow T. Robot.
Dear Miss, Sir, or Madame,
I can no longer sit idly by
on my little robot haunches,
and watch Caucasian actors being
continually cast in non-Caucasian roles.
Christoper Lee's portrayal
of Fu Manchu is a crystalline
example of the phenomenon I have tried,
titled, Bad Actors, Bad Decisions.
(sniffs)
Sorry.
This insidious tradition
of casting, has formed
a psychological backdrop,
in which we play out
the insignificant comings and
goings of our daily lives.
Let me, Crow T. Robot, pull
back the curtain, to reveal
the lie, on which your life is based.
Sign post number one on
your road to discovery,
George Pal's enchanting,
The Seven Faces of Dr. Lao.
Would it shock you to know that
all seven faces were played
by the white, musical
theater actor, Tony Randall?
Wake up, people!
That's seven examples right there.
Now you're saying to yourself,
"Please, Mr. Robot, carrier of
the gleaming sword of truth,
"don't spoil the shining obelisk
"of Sunday afternoon
enjoyment, Charlie Chan."
Sorry, it's my job.
Charlie Chan is a Swede,
named Warner Oland.
"Crow, stop now!
"You're woozy!"
No, the truth is a runaway train.
Who's that playing an Asian in
The Tea House of The August Moon?
It's your precious method
actor, Marlon Brando.
Here's a bonus.
The Indian Chief on F Troop
was a grade-D actor, Frank Nakoa.
Dare I go on?
(crying)
What's the point?
- Crow, buddy, control yourself.
You're getting off track.
The kids out there love
your acerbic editorials.
Stick it to the man!
You can't let them down.
- But it hurts too much.
- Buck up, Crow.
Get out there and do it for the kids!
Come on!
(crying)
- Okay.
Anyway, where was I?
So, in conclusion, Cameron
Mackintosh, bite me!
Oh, wait.
There are so many examples I should give.
What about Joey Bishop in Sergeants 3?
Hey, wait a minute, I like
Joey Bishop in that movie.
He's in a category by himself.
He's always good, no
matter what role he plays.
Regis Philbin had no right to walk
off his show the way he did.
How could he do that?
Why?
(crying)
- No.
Joel, help us.
- Look at what you've
done to my little friends.
Are you guys happy now?
Come on, it's okay, buddy.
- Don't you care?
Don't you even care?
- Our data is showing deep,
deep pain, all around.
Well, it looks like we could expect
to get a Nobel Prize for evil, Frank.
(laughing)
(gasping)
- Better send 'em a commercial.
(upbeat pop music)
- [Joel] Oh, it's not that bad.
- [Servo] It's pretty bad.
- [Joel] Not more.
- [Servo] Tell a joke.
- Oh, Laurel and Hardy are there.
(laughs)
- [Servo] That's a good one.
- I have a pass to see the governor.
- [Joel] I was in Victor Victoria.
- [Servo] Here, let me see that.
"Please excuse Carol from," what is this?
- [Man] Open the gate!
(clears throat)
- [Joel] Now close it, real fast.
(laughs)
- That girl!
- [Servo] Hmm.
(gun shots)
- [Servo] Oh, no!
Bob Hope is killing people!
- Take that you fez monsters.
(gun shot)
- [Joel] Pull!
(laughs)
- [Servo] Oh, it's got flare.
- I guess that means come on.
- [Servo] Oh, Mrs. Peel, we're needed.
- [Joel] Two stairs
diverge into a yellow wood.
- [Servo] Looks like Graceland.
Graceland, Memphis, Tennessee.
- I see Elvis.
(gasps)
- [Servo] Where?
Where?
- Carry me, carry me!
Hey, pile on Uncle Bob.
Tickle machine, tickle machine.
- [Joel] Does this bug you?
I'm not touching you.
Does this bug you?
- [Servo] Oh, bloodless guards.
- [Crow] Thorazine guards.
(laughs)
(humming)
(yells)
- [Servo] Yawn.
(screams)
- [Joel] It's the killer joke.
(laughs)
Sure glad I dressed to move.
You?
- [Crow] Mm.
(gunshots)
Jawbreaker?
- [Servo] Chester A. Arthur?
Ooh, the press shot us a buffalo there.
- [Joel] Mommy?
- Boy, could you tell me what day it is?
- [Joel] Why, it's Christmas Day, sir.
- Mutt?
Mutt?
(dog barking)
- [Joel] Grover Cleveland?
- [Servo] Oh, there you are.
(laughs)
- Hey, who hasn't had
a nightmare like this?
- [Servo] My lord.
Oh, oh, it's you guys again.
Hello.
(whimpering)
- Oh, swords, smimatars.
Hmm.
(laughs)
- [Man Running] Guards!
- [Servo] Alright,
everybody, it's a B Major.
- [Joel] He's being
attacked by a swing choir.
- Kareem!
- [Joel] Oh, he's standing
on an office chair.
- Oh.
- Lin Tang?
- Yes, father.
- [Servo] Hello, we
are your new neighbors.
May we borrow some pesto?
(gasps)
- [Fu Manchu] Proceed, daughter.
- [Servo] Okay.
- [Joel] If you don't look
good, we don't look good.
Oops.
(laughs)
- Sorry, I missed.
- [Joel] And now the cast of My Fair Lady.
- You have fought well.
We are grateful to you, for
opening the doors to us.
- It was nothing.
- [Servo] Nothing.
- We were able to approach unseen.
- We are very happy to serve you.
- Check please!
- [Servo] Uh-oh.
- [Joel] A rat-ta-tat-tat.
Rat-ta-tat-tat.
(gunshots)
- [Servo] Bob Hope is The Mechanic.
- Isn't she helpful?
- [Joel] Over there.
(grunts)
He's strict, that one.
- [Servo] Boy, let me tell ya.
Ooh.
- [Joel] I'll be over
here, if you need me.
- Bring them to my father.
- And bring me to an orthodontist.
- [Servo] I'll say.
- [Fu Manchu] She fights like a man.
- [Servo] But she breaks,
just like a little girl.
- [Lin Tang] We must kill her.
- You may serve us yet.
- I serve only one master.
- [Servo] But I'm good at it.
- We shall see.
Take her away.
- [Joel] Karen Valentine.
- [Servo] She's a good egg.
- [Lin Tang] Why do you keep her alive?
She's dangerous.
- [Fu Manchu] I have my reasons.
- Okay, Mr. CEO.
- [Joel] Filmed in Ivana Trump's bathroom.
(flatulence)
- Whoops, the King's on his throne.
- [Fu Manchu] This will make
an excellent headquarters.
- And Omar Pasha?
- The governor is still in residence.
I shall announce that the
castle was attacked by bandits.
The attack failed, the
bandits were liquidated.
- Along with some factory
second Naugahyde furniture.
- We have one week.
- [Joel] You mean starting the day, now.
You mean including the day, wait a minute.
- [Servo] Meanwhile, on the
hallowed halls of Wossamotta U.
- Continue checking every hour.
Report to me anything
unusual, anything at all.
(mumbles)
Oh, Petrie.
- Don't call me Fifi at the office, dear.
- An imbecile, and an incompetent dolt.
- Did you come all the way to
Scotland Yard to tell me that?
- [Joel] You sweet talker.
- I'm terribly excited,
but I just found this.
It's been on my old bookshelf
for all these years.
- [Crow] It's called Crazy
Cop, can you believe it?
- Mm-hmm.
The world's top authority.
- Well, I dare say, Petrie --
- [All] Dish.
- Would you explain why this book of yours
has suddenly become so important?
- Because his theory may give us the clue
that we are desperately searching for.
Well, you see, he has a
theory that when the chemical
properties of ordinary water, as such that
they lend themselves to transformation --
- [Servo] Bet this clown has
his underwear on backwards.
- [Joel] Mm-hmm.
- Tampered with.
He goes on to say here --
- [Joel] Why are they dubbing the British?
- [Servo] I don't know.
This is terrible.
- [Crow] Let's see.
He grabbed her heaving breasts, oh, sorry.
My notes.
- [Petrie] Prepared by the
letters, which are not as yet,
practicable to man, by
dramatically changes temperature
to a cold so intense --
(buzzes)
- [Servo] Help me.
- Now, provided that you've
got sufficient quantity
of water, the pressure will build up,
which will eventually,
with the crystals --
- [Servo] Really?
- But these crystals of which he writes,
what will they be composed of?
- Possibly a derivative of --
- [Servo] What, are you Carol
Burnett all of a sudden?
- [Man] Excuse me, Sir Dennis.
- What is it?
- From Istanbul, sir.
Attack on the headquarters of the governor
of Anatolia, they were all killed.
- [Servo] I love you.
(kiss smack)
- What about the Bible now, Petrie?
The hand of providence.
- I don't understand.
- [Sir Dennis] Anatolia --
- East of Java.
- [Sir Dennis] Is the
largest source of supply
in the world of the opium poppy.
- [Petrie] By heavens, I was right!
- [Joel] I love opium!
- First of all, I want to have a word
with your Professor Heracles.
- I anticipated you'll try to get in touch
with Heracles through the University.
- He's gone on a trip to
the Middle East in Turkey.
- Turkey!
- [Crow] That's what I'm hungry for!
Turkey and Swiss!
- Anatolia, perhaps.
- [Servo] Anatolia twice.
- [Joel] Meanwhile, at Giro Castle.
(upbeat pop music)
- [Servo] Just a typical
morning for Burt Young.
- [Joel] Oh, here comes Peter
O'Toole and Albert Finney.
- [Servo] When you're
serious about weight loss.
- Hi, sunshine.
You look bright-eyed this morning.
- [Servo] Read me a story.
- [Joel] Once upon a time, there was
a very naughty man named Fu Manchu.
- You will come to the laboratory.
- [Joel] And he had a
spooky-wooky daughter.
- [Crow] Ooh.
- I am perfectly well
aware of the condition
of your heart, Professor.
However, I can keep you alive.
- Not forever.
I'm growing weaker.
In spite of your drugs, I'm going to die.
- There are ways of persuasion.
- I'm no use to you dead.
Within a week, perhaps
before, I shall be dead.
- [Crow] Ooh.
- We shall see.
- [Servo] I'd like two
espressos over here, please.
- [Joel] Yes, my little friend,
Drew, sent these over for you.
- Wow, they make strong drinks there.
(dramatic music)
He just injected it into the mattress.
- [Servo] Doh!
Here, now give this back to Sid and Nancy.
- [Joel] You know, I'm
learning a lot more about this
guy's nasal hair, than I
ever really wanted to know.
- [Servo] Yeah, me too.
- You are going to remain
alive, Professor Heracles.
- [Servo] And stoned off your flabby butt.
- I understand you consulted
a brilliant, young specialist last year.
What was his name?
- Howser.
Doogie Howser.
- He's in London, but he would never
help you, even to save my life.
- Indeed.
- Not even Kessler can save me.
Don't you understand?
My heart.
- [Joel] Becky?
Tom?
Are you in there?
- It's died.
- [Servo] Hmm?
Mosquito.
- There are other, younger
hearts in the world.
- Dad, like I'm almost sure.
Gag me.
- Stronger hearts.
- [Servo] Say, who's the new guy?
- Geez, he's had his nipples sanded off.
(groans)
- [Servo] Him again.
- [Joel] Does he please you?
Does he bring you pleasure?
(seagulls chirping)
- [Servo] Oh sure.
Go ahead and barge right into London.
(laughs)
It was funny the first time.
- We now return to those magnificent men,
and their jaunty jalopies,
on your Channel Nine movie.
(humming)
- [Servo] Masterpiece Theatre continues
with the Jewel and the Crown.
- [Joel] It's Audrey Hepburn in Charade.
(humming)
- [Servo] You know, personally,
I would've worn a
slingback with those shoes.
- [Joel] You would?
- [Servo] Yeah.
- Did the director take his lessons
in walking scenes from Roger Corman?
- [Servo] Look, nobody's following you!
- [Crow] Huh.
- [Joel] They switched
to Tungsten, I think.
- I've been eatin' berries all day.
(laughs)
- [Servo] Does she, or doesn't she?
- [Joel] The Dutch Masters at home!
- [Kessler] Yes, yes, yes, Mrs. Ward.
- [Crow] No, no, no.
- [Kessler] No.
- [Crow] Yes.
- No, no, no, no.
- [Crow] Yes, it is.
- Every night, Ward.
- [Crow] No.
- [Kessler] Yes.
- [Crow] Yes.
- Yes.
- [Crow] No, you don't say.
You don't say.
- [Servo] Who was it?
- He didn't say.
(laughs)
- Thank you, thank you very much.
(bell dings)
- You don't have any
more patients, do you?
- No.
- [Joel] No, I can't watch another frame.
- I'm afraid I can't come yet.
I'm expecting someone.
- [Woman] Oh, someone important?
- Oh, yes.
One, a doctor I know slightly,
from the Home Office,
and other's from Scotland Yard.
- So, they found you out at last?
- Oh, yes.
(knocks on door)
Right on time.
Ingrid, I sent Miss Lawrence home.
Would you?
- Of course.
- [Joel] I'll also send
Miss Lawrence home.
- Thank you, thank you very much.
- [Servo] Now, time for a Bloody Mary.
(phone rings)
- Yes, that would be the phone.
- Dr. Kessler.
Who?
- [Servo] Not who, Fu!
- Oh, yes, Sir Charles.
No, no, no, no, I'm afraid I
can't attend a dinner tonight.
- [Joel] Right this way.
- [Kessler] An important case, yes.
- [Joel] Very good now.
Now, just put on that paper gown,
and in get in the stirrups.
Thank you.
- [Dr. Kessler] Thank you very much.
Goodbye.
- We introduced ourselves.
Dr. Kessler, this is Dr. Petrie,
Sir Dennis Nayland Smith.
(laughs)
- We're old friends, met on holiday.
We fished the same river.
(laughs)
(mumbles)
- [Servo] Balderdash.
There's no work to do.
- Dr. Kessler, we want some information
about Professor Heracles.
He is your patient, isn't he?
- Yes, patient and friend,
but he has a very severe cardio condition.
- [Joel] So I don't like him anymore.
- Do you know where he is now?
- Well, here's a stab, Joe's Bar?
- He called me last week,
to tell me he's going to the continent.
- [Servo] No, no, you fool!
He's incontinent.
- Some days ago I had a card from Athens.
- [Joel] She turned into a mannequin.
- [Kessler] Look, I've
go it here, somewhere.
If I can just find it.
- [Crow] Hmm, not bad.
Later, later.
- [Servo] Oh, no, that's disgusting.
A picture of you and Oliver Reed.
- What the devil is he
doing so far from England?
- He mentions on the card that
he's moving on to Istanbul.
- Istanbul?
What's he doing, the circular trip?
(knocks on door)
- Ingrid --
- [Crow] Get some more actors
in this scene, will you?
- Would you please tell
them that I'm busy?
- Yes, yes, don't worry.
I'll send them away.
- [Crow] Hey, let's not
clue the audience in
on the plot yet, okay?
- [Joel] Let's ditch her, huh?
- [Servo] Would you like
one of our watchtowers?
(percussive music)
- Does this bug you?
Does this bug you?
I'm not touching you.
- [Joel] Doggone, take me away.
- I know nothing about
Heracles' experiments --
- [Servo] Nothing!
Nothing!
- He would want to benefit
mankind, not to destroy it.
- Fu Manchu is only
interested in destruction.
- [Crow] Hey, he's making
a Xerox copy of his butt.
- [Servo] Hey, what do you know?
- I believe it's a question
of saving the world, Dr. Kessler.
- [Servo] Oh, that.
- [Joel] Leave the
specimens alone, please.
- [Servo] I think it would
be fun to go to Istanbul.
- [Joel] Oh, that would be fun.
- Well then, if I may, I will come
with you, and maybe Ingrid, too.
- Good.
- Thank you.
- [Joel] We'll make it a
holiday, a camping holiday.
- [Crow] Damn, this
tobacco is really good.
(knocks on door)
- [Joel] Only you can prevent desk fires.
- [Servo] Land shark.
- Tickle-Ray.
- [Joel] Miss Jane Pittman.
- [Servo] Time for go to bed.
- [Sir Dennis] I wonder
what's keeping Kessler?
- Gee, this is the most
action we've seen, so far.
- [Joel] Smells like
a dead monkey in here.
You?
- [Servo] It's not funny anymore, guys.
I can't take this anymore.
I'm getting out of here.
Get me out of here please.
- [Joel] Oh, geez, come on.
Okay, jeepers.
- [Servo] This film is too terrible.
- Kessler didn't mean to
leave a cigarette burn,
into a polished wood table.
(upbeat pop music)
- Ah, come in, Red Shriner
Sergeant-At-Arms Joel.
This is Black Shriner Leader, Tom.
Come in boys, and cut the comedy.
I'm in trouble here.
Over.
- [Joel] Ah, yeah, Shriner Leader Tom,
this is Red Shriner
Joel, at your backdoor,
with Neon Peon Crow in tow.
What's your 20?
- What's my 20?
Sweet Sons of Norway, man!
My magic carpet's malfunctioned,
and I'm stuck in front
of the Robert Hall store,
on the Main Street.
On top of that, I've run
out of Jolly Rancher candy,
and the kids are startin' to look ugly.
Over.
- [Crow] Ace to ya, good buddy.
This is the Neon Peon.
I'm in your rockin' chair.
Hold tight, Shriner Leader Joel and I,
about to do a flyover.
- Hurry up, man.
I'm running out of hard candy.
Condition red.
Send in the clowns.
What's the use?
(crying)
- Aw, man, Joel.
He's totally off script.
There's nothing that says anything
about sounding like a broken man.
- Yeah, you're right.
Let's see, it says here, Tom says,
"Tighten formation, men,
those kids are all over me.
"Argh."
It just says, "Argh," it doesn't say
anything about sobbing pitifully.
- I can't do it, guys.
I just can't do it.
I can't go through another
sketch, loosely based
on some vague reference of the movie.
There are only a few kinds
of fezzes in this movie,
and suddenly, we're the
Sahara Shriners, riding flying
carpets on Maxwell Street Days.
Why?
Get me out of here.
- I don't understand.
How is this sketch any different
than anything else we do, during a movie?
- Well, Crow, it's not the
sketch, it's this movie.
Look at him.
He's just a broken man.
- You're tellin' me.
There are absolutely no psychological
footholds in this film.
It's like trying to climb El Capitan.
There's something wrong with me!
Why!
(sobbing)
- Better you than me.
- Oh, Crow, come on.
Look at what you've done to him.
- Me?
- Do you see what you've done to this guy?
Come on!
- You see, Frank, it feels good
to be with the winners, doesn't it?
- Oh, yes.
- Hey, let's order out.
Mongolian?
- I was thinking more
along the lines of one
of those delightful, stuffed
pesto pizzas from Eduardo's.
- Hmm, you fly, I'll buy.
- Solid, Jackson.
(laughs)
Oh, bite me.
It's fun.
- Thank you, Frankie.
Now, Joely, you and your scaredy-bots,
up great, deep, drafts of the second half
of this stink-burger, called
The Castle of Fu Manchu.
Ain't that a man?
(buzzing)
(yelling)
- We've got movie siren!
Let's hit it, boys!
(crying)
Oh, it's okay.
- In two copies.
- [Servo] Two coffees?
(cries)
- I know you will be able to
follow, without any trouble.
Goodbye, Melnik.
- [Crow] But I'm not leaving.
Oh, I see.
You don't have to knock me over the head.
- Lieutenant, sir?
- [Servo] I feel a little bit better.
- [Man] Go away.
- [Joel] Order lunch.
That'll take a while.
- [Servo] Thanks, guys.
- [Man] Oh, go.
- [Servo] What, do you need a
ton of bricks to fall on ya?
- Goodbye, Sergeant.
(yells)
- [Servo] Meanwhile, in east Dubuque.
- [Joel] It's Nessie!
- It's the Boss!
It's Springsteen!
- [Man] A boat approaches!
- [Servo] But keep it quiet!
We got a super secret plan!
(laughs)
- Methinks the King approaches.
- [Joel] Oh, darn escalator's out again.
Got trapped on there once.
- [Man] Lin Tang arrives
with the prisoners.
- They could use an extension line.
- [Fu Manchu] Very well.
- [Joel] I'm done tanning, thanks.
- [Servo] Under this robe, I'm
naked as the day I was born.
Riding free and easy.
(laughs)
- You don't think there's much chance
he'll fall down those stairs?
- [Servo] No.
Wishful thinking.
(boat engine whirring)
- [Joel] Hi-kee-bah.
- [Servo] Suddenly, I
have the urge to, um.
- What are you looking at?
- [Joel] We'll be right back, after this.
- Come back here!
(grunts)
Where are you going?
- To Scarborough Fair?
- I must see your master.
- [Man] Get out of here!
- [Joel] That guy's gonna be
a sophomore for five years, man.
- I bring you valuable information.
- [Servo] I bring tidings of great joy.
- It's all lined up.
- [Omar] Start talking then --
- [Servo] And start chalking.
- [Joel] Well, once upon a
time, there were three bears.
- [Servo] Cher's getting
back with Gregg Allman.
(gasps)
- Lin Tang was here today, in Istanbul.
She took two prisoners away with her.
- [Joel] Justine Bateman
has a new movie coming out.
- Yes, yes.
Of course, I do not know who,
but I know which way they went.
- Well?
(breathing heavily)
- The same road Lisa took,
Master, to the other side.
(kiss smacks)
- [Joel] You smell like a fresh cookie.
- To Anatolia.
- [Crow] You're dripping sweat on me.
- Ahmet!
Reward him.
- [Joel] Oh, someone's got an oily t-zone.
- [Servo] Where's his reward?
(screams)
No, no, I meant give him a slice of pie.
- I'm so wasted, I forgot what he said.
- [Servo] A waste.
- [Crow] No, never.
- [Joel] Oh, it's the Istanbul Orkin man.
- [Servo] I'd say this
movie has less action than
a Who's Life Is It Anyway?
- [Joel] I'm a sailor.
(laughs)
- Will you help me?
(ominous music)
- [Servo] What, what?
What?
- [Joel] No.
No!
Oh.
- [Servo] Michael Caine and
Nancy Kulp are vampires.
- [Joel] Shoot, roommates!
- David Bowie, from The Hunger.
- [Servo] And he's all dewy.
Dewy Bowie.
- [Joel] I hate jet lag.
- Boy, I really racked up the
frequent flyer miles though.
- [Servo] Yeah, frequent dyer miles.
(laughs)
- [Joel] Dece.
You're feelin' better.
- [Servo] A little.
- Kessler!
Ingrid!
- [Servo] In color.
- She's kinda overdressed for espionage.
- Professor Heracles.
(heavy breathing)
- [Joel] She had to sit
next to the stinky guy.
(laughs)
- [Servo] Oh, I can't watch this.
I mean, I can't see this.
- [Joel] It's kinda like a
Metallica video, but slower.
- [Servo] Oh, come on, what
is this, Kirlian photography?
- Yeah, Moe, Larry, and
Kirlian photography.
(laughs)
- Geez, and I thought City of
Hope was an underlit movie.
(groans)
They've been candied.
Candide?
- [Servo] Candide.
- Where are we?
- [Joel] You're one step away
from never working again.
- Anatolia.
He had a boss for us.
- They've turned us into Warhols.
- It's incredible.
Who were those people?
- [Joel] Who are these people?
- They were kidnapped,
by the men of Fu Manchu.
- Fu Man --
- Manchu.
Spit it out, honey.
- I can't move, but feel I'm paralyzed.
- You'll be alright in a few minutes.
They used my crystals against you.
- [Servo] This is the first color movie
that needs to be colorized.
(laughs)
- But in a small dose.
(groans)
- Professor!
- [Joel] Look, you're overtired.
We'll talk to you later.
(laughs)
- She could use a good clay pack.
- [Joel] Mm-hmm.
Spores.
- [Servo] Come on.
Meanwhile, in downtown Duluth.
- [Joel] It's not funny.
- [Servo] I went to Istanbul,
and all I got was this lousy fez, huh?
(laughs)
It's funny.
- Hey, take a long walk off that thing.
- [Servo] Yeah.
- [Joel] Hi, we're the Boatniks.
(laughs)
- Inspector Ahmet?
- [Crow] You inspect her, I'm busy.
- Told that we'd expect you here.
- An honor, sir, but I'm
afraid that I have bad news.
- What is the bad news, Inspector?
- [Servo] My hat.
- The bandits, who attacked the castle,
were Omar Pasha's men.
- Omar Pasha?
- [Inspector] He controls the opium trade.
- Opium?
- [Crow] The perfume?
- An informer called Melnik,
appeared this morning, killed.
(buzzing)
- [Servo] Tell me again, please.
I need your help, please.
- His last visit, yesterday,
was to Omar Pasha's coffee shop.
♫ Omar Pasha ♫
(laughs)
- [Inspector] I should
have listened to him.
- Why?
- Omar Pasha has vanished.
- Meanwhile, in, oh, forget it.
(sighs)
- [Voiceover] That he
has gone to Anatolia,
to rescue the girl, Lisa, and
is camped opposite the castle,
on the other side of the --
- [Joel] Looks like two seals
waterskiing, doesn't it?
- [Crow] Uh-huh.
- [Joel] Kind of?
- [Crow] No.
(singing in foreign language)
♫ Oh, lord, it's hard to be humble ♫
- [Servo] Uh-oh.
- Hey, it's the grand wizard himself.
- [Joel] What a burn, wow.
(thud)
(yells)
- Come on!
- [Servo] Thank you, thank you.
Next show at 10 o'clock.
Thank you very much.
- [Joel] Hey, don't step on the guy.
(laughs)
Come on.
- [Man] All is clear, master.
- [Servo] Oh, geez, I thought
Shriners helped people.
- [Joel] Rock the Casbah, dude.
- [Servo] Sharif don't like it.
- Wouldn't it be great
if we knew who they were,
where they are, or what they were doing?
- [Servo] Pretty much.
- [Joel] Well, he looks
like a Century 21 salesman.
- [Crow] Gandhi's back, and he's stuffed.
- Fu Manchu.
- [Fu Manchu] Bring
forth the two prisoners,
Dr. Kessler and Dr. Ingrid Cox.
- [Lin Tang] Yes, father.
The guards are bringing them.
- [Servo] Oh, look, it's the
original hand-hammered wok.
- It looks like stainless steel from here.
- [Servo] Oh, yeah, you're right.
- [Joel] Love me.
- [Fu Manchu] I have brought
you here to save the life
of someone, whose knowledge I require,
as a thirsty man needs water.
- [Crow] Tonight on, You Asked For It.
- Crystal clear water, Dr. Kessler.
- [Joel] Crystal blue persuasion.
- [Servo] Ah, cripes, this again.
- The name of the person to whom
I refer, is Professor Heracles.
- [Servo] Uh, we're underwhelmed.
(laughs)
You know, Burt Young has looked worse.
- [Joel] Mm-hmm.
- Well, he's Burt Young alright.
- [Dr. Kessler] He is dying.
- [Ingrid] Professor.
- You will use your skill, doctor.
You will make him live.
- [Crow] Dammit, fool!
I'm a surgeon, not a doctor.
- I am not a miracle worker.
Besides, you took everything
away, except my hands.
- On the contrary, Dr. Kessler --
- [Servo] Et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
- You will find everything
here, that you require.
- [Joel] Let's see what's
behind door number one.
- [Crow] Ooh.
- [Servo] Here, I have
everything you need.
I threw in the hairy,
naked man, just for kicks.
- [Joel] Nice touch.
- [Dr. Kessler] What's
wrong with that man?
- [Crow] Nothing at all.
- [Fu Manchu] There is nothing
wrong with him, doctor.
He is in perfect physical condition.
- [Joel] I'll say.
- And unlike Professor Heracles,
his heart is as sound as a bell.
- [Servo] Bong.
- Do you not agree, doctor,
that Professor Heracles
should have that splendid heart?
- [Joel] If it comes
with that beefy chest.
- [Dr. Kessler] But that
man is not dead or dying.
- [Crow] He's only mostly dead!
- He is drugged.
He will die for the sake of science.
- And for your sake, also.
- I need Heracles to complete my plans.
I need him alive, conscious, coherent --
- [Servo] I wish this movie
were conscious or coherent!
(cries)
- If I refuse?
- I hadn't thought of that.
Gosh, he's clever.
- Then Dr. Ingrid Cox will die
an extremely painful death.
- No!
- [Joel] No fresh ground pepper with that?
- The choice is yours, Dr. Kessler.
- [Servo] Well?
- In order to convince you, I
shall arrange a demonstration.
- No!
- [Servo] No, no.
What's goin' on?
- Glenn Manning, get off that dam!
- [Joel] Bridge on the River Kwai.
- [Servo] Looks like it, doesn't it?
- [Joel] Biggest crack by a dam site.
(laughs)
Yep, right there.
- Hey, there's a little Dutch boy
putting his finger in there.
- [Servo] Where?
- [Man] Run!
Run for you lives!
- [Servo] Run men!
- [Joel] The plot's
starting to make sense.
Run!
- [Servo] This dam scene.
- Hey, don't forget to punch out!
- [Joel] You know, I suddenly
have to go to the bathroom.
- [Crow] Really?
- [Joel] Yep.
- [Servo] Why, I wonder?
- [Joel] Funniest thing.
- You know, they might need some
Thompson's WaterSeal up there.
- [Servo] I think
something to hold it back.
Don't worry, men!
It's the Egyptians who are gonna get us!
Pharaoh and the gang.
(clicking)
Yay, we're getting off early!
Free day.
- Force 10 from Navarone
- [Joel] Oh, quit grovelling.
- [Servo] Gravelling.
(screaming)
Uh-huh.
Yep, yep.
You know, cutting it faster
doesn't make it any more exciting.
- [Crow] Ah.
- [Servo] Oh, that's a relief.
- [Joel] I didn't think
that dam would ever break.
- [Servo] Uh-uh.
Oh, the Rolling Stones.
Doesn't do much for me.
(rumbling)
It's kind of convulsive, isn't it?
(laughs)
- You have got to be kidding me.
- [Servo] This isn't very good.
- [Joel] Prince of Tides.
- The River, with Mel
Gibson and Sissy Spacek.
- [Joel] You know, I miss
the water slide at the Dells.
- [Servo] I wonder.
Oh, look, rock made out of water.
- Complete annihilation.
- I am the god of hydrotherapy.
- Even Nayland Smith cannot
touch you now, father.
- I wish that he would try.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] We'll be back,
after these messages.
- [Servo] Meanwhile, in
Two Harbors, Minnesota.
You must kill Kurtz.
Terminate with extreme prejudice.
- I wish this film had some news for me.
(mumbles)
- This is Asia.
- [Servo] Could we see
specific sites in Asia?
- [Inspector] I must leave you, gentlemen.
- Thank you, Inspector, for all your help.
I'm sorry, Petrie, but
this is where we part.
- Speaking of part, comb that hair.
- It's better that way.
You can be of more use to me in Istanbul.
- [Joel] Stuffed on a mantel.
- [Petrie] How?
- I want you to telegraph the
Home Secretary's office in London.
- [Petrie] Mm-hmm.
- Use the standard code.
Tell them that I intend to try
to get into Fu Manchu's castle.
- But how do you know that Fu
Manchu captured the castle?
Besides, there's nothing
but guesswork to go on.
- I have something here --
- [Joel] Wait, that's Robert Goulet!
- This was found on a dead man --
(groans)
- Still guesswork, Petrie?
- [Joel] Dish?
- Kessler's head cloth!
(mumbles)
- [Ingrid] Curt, you mustn't do this.
- [Servo] Oh, well.
Very well, then.
I will use the toilet.
- Well, can't be that bad.
They put them in the same cell.
- [Servo] Yeah.
- A doctor can't say no to saving a life.
- [Joel] Except when the
patient has no insurance.
- You cannot do this.
If by saving Professor Heracles' life,
you are helping this
murderer in his plans.
- [Servo] Classic tragedy, eh?
- Do you believe that Fu Manchu
will let Heracles live,
after he's used him?
- I don't know.
- [Crow] Much about that,
but I know what I like.
- But we have to try everything.
Nobody before tried to
do such an operation.
- [Joel] You mean the goofy
game for dopey doctors?
- [Servo] Yep.
- Do you --
- Love me?
- [Servo] Do I what?
- Do you think you can do it?
- [Servo] In the road.
- Yes.
(groans)
- [Servo] Sorry.
- [Dr. Kessler] Yes, I know we can do it.
- [Joel] Now that's lipstick
that lasts, from Yardley.
- [Servo] Mm-hmm.
- [Kessler] I hope.
- I'm so ashamed.
- Are you sure --
- [Joel] Bees can fly?
- You're not doing all this
for me, just to save my life?
- [Servo] Well, look.
I just wanted to get to first base
with you, and things snowballed.
- What?
Oh, were you talking?
Sorry.
- [Kessler] We have not a chance.
In this moment --
- [Joel] You know, it's kind of like
watching the Hollywood Squares.
- [Kessler] Who matters to me.
- [Servo] You are every
woman in the world, to me.
(footsteps)
- [Crow] Have you been
listening the whole time?
I thought this was a private cell.
Sneaky.
- [Servo] This scene is a real strain.
(laughs)
- [Crow] That's grate though, just grate.
- [Servo] No.
- Yes, we know how long this has been on!
Don't shove it in our face!
- [Joel] Tonight, on a
very special Dr. Kildare.
- [Servo] You say ether, and I say either.
(laughs)
Let's call the whole thing off.
- [Joel] Breathe deep,
the gathering gloom.
Watch lights fade in every room.
- [Servo] Oh, this is aromatherapy.
I've seen this before.
(breathes deep)
- Yep, more, more.
Keep it comin', I can take more.
- [Servo] Don't look at me!
Don't look at me, mommy!
Frank Booth.
- Suzy Wong was arraigned in Los Angeles
County Court for
impersonating Marlo Thomas.
- [Joel] I am Suzy Wong.
- [Servo] I am Suzy Wong.
- No, I'm Suzy Wong.
- [Servo] Will the real Suzy Wong --
- [Joel] It's the world of Suzy Wong.
(laughs)
- Okay, who wants a drum stick?
I'm just kidding.
- [Servo] First, we split the
top, and pour in real butter.
(yelling)
- [Joel] Take it easy,
it's just tempera paint.
- [Crow] Okay.
- [Joel] Real blood
doesn't bead like that!
- [Crow] Using cadmium.
- [Servo] Did I take the Hippocratic oath?
- No, you took the hypocritic oath.
(laughs)
- [Servo] Oh, damn, I
thought I did that one.
- I'm a dermatologist, I
have no idea what I'm doing.
- [Joel] He's playing
hangman on this guy's belly.
- Well, I see by the
old clock on the wall,
it's time for more boredom!
- [Joel] I'm Harold Lloyd.
- [Servo] Ooh!
- [Crow] Oh!
(grunts)
- [Servo] Ooh!
- [Crow] Oh!
- [Servo] Ouch.
- [Servo] Ooh!
- [Crow] Ow!
(groans)
(laughs)
Look at this shot.
They should never have let Shatner direct!
- [Joel] Sweating like Tom Jones.
- [Servo] That's not unusual.
- [Joel] What's new, pussycat?
- Yeah, we would you like to try this?
It's kind of fun.
- [Joel] Here, I've got to
go check on the sauce there.
- [Servo] Oh, don't wet the forehead.
The chest, the chest.
- What, are you carving Pinocchio?
(upbeat pop music)
- [Joel] Tap hard once, tap hard twice.
Oh, now you've gotta fix
what you've done wrong.
- What, are you clamping
every individual cell?
Got the whole Dremel kit out.
- [Joel] Man, this scene is so gross,
even the lighting guy left.
- [Servo] He left awhile ago.
- [Joel] Oh, please!
(groaning)
(coughs)
- [Servo] It's just a gizzard!
Save that for the cat.
- [Crow] Oh, Donald.
- [Servo] Ever operate before?
- Nope.
- [Servo] Me neither.
- [Joel] Ooh, his ink pen blew up.
- [Servo] Yeah, look at his fingers.
- Help me, somebody please help me.
- [Servo] I shouldn't have had that,
(gags)
Cobb salad, for lunch.
- You know, they look totally different,
when you open them up.
There's no little numbers.
- [Joel] You know, I am completely
off the manual right now.
I have no idea what I am doing.
It is wild in here.
- What you rootin' around for, tubers?
Close him up!
- [Servo] Crazy clock, a new
novel by Henry (mumbles).
That was fantastic.
You?
- Was it disgusting for you, too?
- [Servo] Kind of looks like
an Annie Leibovitz photo.
(kiss smack)
(exhales)
- I'm spent, I feel so empty.
- [Servo] Well.
Meanwhile, at Shakespeare In The Park.
Hope they're doing Macbeth!
- Gee, I never thought I'd be
grateful to see this scene again.
- A further warning --
- [Servo] Attention, camp,
tonight's movie is My Darling Clementine.
- When the governments of all
the nations do not accept my terms --
- I will be very put out.
- In four day's time, I will
bring desolation to mankind.
- [Servo] But first, a message
for True Value hardware stores.
- Meanwhile, Euell Gibbons
hears the call of nature.
(whistles)
(speaks in foreign language)
- [Joel] Incoming sentence!
(sighs)
- That's easy for you to say.
- [Servo] You know, maybe
there's some deep meaning
to this movie, that
we're just not getting.
Or maybe not.
- He's dying of Legionnaire's disease.
- [Servo] Shriners.
- [Joel] Shriners.
- Oh, oh, yeah.
- [Servo] Don't you wish?
(laughs)
- Typical Shriner.
Smashed his midget Mustang into a pole.
- [Servo] Yep, sad really.
Well, now this con's
sneakin' into a petting zoo.
- Heavy.
- [Joel] Alexander
Monday, It Takes A Thief.
- I'll take those boots, Mr. Bond.
(thud)
- [Servo] How the devil did I do that?
I couldn't do that again, if I tried.
- [Omar] Did you get close to the castle?
- [Servo] Close to Picasso?
- Yes, master.
- Jelly donut got away from you, huh?
- [Omar] Speak.
(dog barking)
- There are 50 men guarding the castle.
- [Joel] Oh, great.
He's the only one who knows
the plot, and he's dying.
- [Servo] Typical.
- Their leader still lives...
Says Fu Manchu's a prisoner.
- It was Callahan!
Callahan did it!
I have my rights.
I have my rights!
- Fu Manchu's work is done.
- [Joel] Come on, put on a happy fez.
(groans)
- What a lovely tap pant.
- Darkoy's headband.
- [Servo] Aykroyd's?
- Bury this man with honor.
- Right, sir.
I'll put him in the dumpster.
- [Servo] No, no.
(yells)
Who are you?
- Manix!
(humming)
- Hold, you fools.
- Tell your men to drop their arms.
Quickly!
Don't move, any of you.
- [Servo] It could be a trick.
He didn't say Simon says.
- I am Omar Pasha.
- And I'm Nayland Smith of Scotland Yard.
- I thought I could smell a policeman.
- It seems that, for once, you
and I could be on the same side.
(laughs)
- [Joel] That would be fun.
- I too seek Fu Manchu.
- [Servo] Well, gesundheit.
- We now return to Burt Young
in, The Mickey Rooney Story.
(humming)
I'm sorry I locked us in, okay?
Look, I'm here, too.
I'm not happy about it either!
- You have done well, Dr. Kessler.
- His recovery will take a long time.
- We cannot afford to wait
for complete recovery.
- [Joel] It's real pricey.
- As soon as he regains consciousness,
he will be made to talk.
- And if Heracles refuses?
- Need I remind you, doctor,
that he has no alternative.
- Oh, thanks, the new light helps.
- If I refuse to help you any further?
- Then you will sign this
lady's death warrant.
- [Servo] Sure, got a pen?
- Your help during the
operation, was invaluable.
We have no further use for you.
- [Ingrid] No!
(crying)
- [Servo] I amuse me.
(laughs)
- Look after your patient, doctor.
- [Servo] Please.
- And watch him well.
- Tonight, on a very
violent Medical Center.
(thwack)
- Curt!
- [Servo] Wait, wait, you
guys got me all wrong.
I'm a veterinary technician.
- Father, the guards have caught --
- [Joel] That girl.
- Omar Pasha.
- Alone?
- Yes, and unarmed, as
if he invited capture.
- Anything to end the pain.
- [Fu Manchu] Have the
girl, Lisa, brought to me.
- [Lin Tang] Yes, father.
♫ My white knight, not ♫
- I've got a crazy
idea, but it just might,
oh, forget it.
- [Joel] Let me out of here!
- [Servo] Let us out of here.
Oh, it's Paloma Picasso,
right where she belongs.
- Who are you?
- [Joel] Anjelica Huston.
- Lisa.
- Did they do that to you?
- No, she thought it would be cute.
Of course they did it.
- [Joel] This movie is
taking its toll on me.
(deeply exhales)
- [Servo] Me too, let's get outta here.
- I think this is the worst
one they've ever managed to do.
(crying)
Wow, that one really stung.
- Yeah.
- It's a tough one, isn't it?
- Yeah, whatever.
- Boy, I'd hate to meet this movie
in a dark alley, some night, huh?
- Yeah, sure, whatever.
- Hey, Tom, you got a little --
- No, no, don't, don't --
- No, really, you got a little --
- No, just stop it okay!
Just stop it!
I won't see it.
This is terrible!
(mumbles)
- Jeepers.
- Oh, what's the deal
with Fu Manchu anyways?
It's not like he's really
evil, he's just dull.
It's like some twisted
bureaucrat in silk 'jamas.
- It's terrible.
- I'm really glad you
brought that up, Crow,
because I happen to have
some artist renderings.
- [Both] Oh, no!
- Oh, come on.
Come on, it'll add a little levity, okay?
This is the story of Fu Manchu, okay?
- I don't care.
- [Joel] Fu Manchu was
born Carl Ivanchu --
- Ivan?
Oh, that's terrible.
- [Joel] In Schenectady,
New York, in 1916.
His parents, David Wayne
and Patricia Ann Chu,
owned the Superior
Skate and Blade Company.
- [Servo] Skate?
- [Joel] A thriving ice skate
and cutlery business in 1931.
- [Servo] Not cutlery.
- [Joel] Young Carl's
father became very ill,
and they sold the business --
- [Servo] Did he die?
- [Joel] And moved the family
to Appleton, Wisconsin.
- [Servo] Oh, no, not Appleton.
- A move that broke his heart.
Yeah, it's gets better
though, it gets better.
Okay, a short year
later, ignoring the pleas
of his heartbroken family,
he moved, by himself,
to New York City, the Big Apple.
His dream, to make it on
Broadway, the great white way.
- [Servo] Was his dream shattered?
(sniffs)
- [Crow] You copied
these off the New Yorker.
- [Joel] No, he began his career
as most young hopefuls do,
running cigarettes for Agnes de Mille.
- [Servo] Agnes de Mille!
- [Crow] Oh, no!
- [Joel] This kept him
busy for 12 hours a day,
and nearly broke his spirit.
He was on one of his many
trips to the store for a carton
of Camels, that he hit upon what was --
- [Servo] Camels?
- [Joel] To become his
favorite stage name.
The story goes, that a panhandler
asked him for a nickel
to, "Get some food, man."
- [Servo] No, not the pun!
- [Joel] Well, Carl liked
that, and that's all it took.
His name was Fu Manchu, okay?
- [Crow] Oh, that's terrible.
- [Joel] After a brief
stint running sandwiches
for Fatty Arbuckle, he got a job,
sweeping the streets in a clown outfit.
- [Crow] Not a clown outfit.
- [Servo] No, not a clown!
(yelling)
(crying)
- [Joel] Okay, now, no, clowns are fun.
The idea caught and soon,
Fu Manchu was managing
over a dozen clown street sweepers.
He was now in a position to return
to his first love, dinner theater.
- [Servo] Oh, I'm gonna be sick.
- [Joel] Okay, here we go.
His first role was as
the lovable Betty in,
Let's Drink A Toast To Crazy Legs.
A short-lived, off-Broadway musical,
starring Danny Thomas
and Charles Nelson --
- [Servo] No, no, no!
(cries)
- What's the use?
Why am I up here?
What are you doing to us?
(crying)
- Auntie Em, Auntie Em!
(laughs)
- Way to go, doctor.
- [Both] Woo!
- Yes.
- Well, we've finally got
you on the run, eh, booby?
Frank, there's some pie in the kitchen.
Why don't you go slice us up a couple
of nice, big slabs of French silk, huh?
Don't skimp.
- Yes, sir!
- As for you, Macaulay Culkin,
get back into that theater,
after this message, of course.
(upbeat pop music)
(dramatic music)
(crying)
- Gonna make it?
- [Servo] They grabbed the girl,
and turned her into a guy in a fez.
- [Joel] He's been eating spaghetti.
Ian Cronin.
- [Crow] So, you didn't
call a cab then, huh?
- Is this the way --
- [Joel] To San Jose?
- To greet a stranger in your house?
- You are no stranger to me, Omar Pasha.
- [Joel] Only a friend I haven't met yet.
(laughs)
- But I never thought you to be a fool.
- Fools do not trade --
- [Servo] Fools rush in.
- With lives.
- [Joel] Where has she been all my death?
- Give her back to me, and I will
give you the head of your enemy.
- [Servo] Alfredo Garcia?
- Enemy?
- Nayland Smith.
- Release him!
- [Joel] And let him love again.
- [Servo] Heel!
♫ Torn between two lovers
♫ Feelin' like a ♫
- My men are camped in the
hills, on the other side --
- The hills are alive.
- Overlooking this castle.
Nayland Smith is their prisoner.
I want this woman.
- Hey, who wouldn't?
- She belongs to me.
- [Joel] I have the pink slip.
- You shall have her, provided
that you give me Nayland Smith.
- You have my word.
- Then you shall remain my guest.
- [Omar] For how long?
- That I shall decide.
- [Servo] You fiend!
You evil, diabolical,
treacherous, wonderful man!
(thwack)
- [Joel] Good aims, you're not.
- [Crow] I was just testing the blade,
I hope you didn't take it the wrong way.
(laughs)
- [Fu Manchu] Let her
go, she cannot escape.
- Not in those slacks.
(thud)
- [Servo] Dad, can I borrow the car?
Uh-oh.
- Take him to the laboratory.
- [Servo] Feed him to the clam.
- [Joel] Now, where did I park, oh!
The giraffe, no.
- [Servo] Boy, she's
really in the dark now.
(laughs)
- [Joel] Sting, stung.
- [Servo] Who timed this
print, Stevie Wonder?
(laughs)
- [Crow] Accepting the award for editing.
- [Joel] It's Evening At
The Improv with Fu Manchu.
- You are an obstinate man.
- Thank you, sir.
- How highly do you value your life,
compared with that of Nayland Smith.
- Try me.
- [Joel] Let's crack the party ball, man.
- The entrance to eternity --
- [Servo] That's bigger
than I thought it would be.
- [Fu Manchu] Which leads
directly to the sea.
Systems of water are poised above it.
A touch of a lever will release hundreds,
of thousands of gallons of water --
- [Servo] Do it.
- Combined with Professor
Heracles' crystals,
this can transform the entire sea,
into one gigantic block of ice.
- [Joel] Which'll be great for parties.
- [Servo] Now then, the Pirates
of Penzance will help you into your chair.
(sighs)
- [Joel] It's Mrs. Sawfull.
Chairman, Ow!
- Inside the Comic Mind with Fu Manchu.
- Where is Nayland Smith?
- [Joel] Who is Nayland Smith?
- If you'll free me and Lisa.
- When we find her.
- [Servo] But right now,
she's doing a blackout sketch.
- My men are camped in the
park, four kilometers from here.
- He's about to become a pencil neck geek.
- [Servo] Uh-oh.
- [Omar] Nayland Smith is with them.
- [Joel] He's really gonna needle him.
(groans)
Oh, wait, he wasn't done yet.
- I had Jello today.
- [Servo] Oh, his gums are bleeding.
He doesn't floss much, does he?
- Next week, on The Castle of Fu Manchu.
- [Joel] Stop doing that.
- Sorry.
- [Joel] They trying to sneak up on us?
- Hey, just drop the
ball, and take a stroke.
- [Servo] For cryin' out loud.
- They'll never find it in that rough.
- [Joel] They're snipe hunting.
Snipe!
- [Servo] At Hazeltine's.
You, you get in the house,
you're embarrassing me.
- It's like the ninja
version of Days of Heaven.
(laughs)
(explosion)
- [Servo] Ooh, stock footage.
Oh, old, vile jelly,
where is thy luster now?
Oedipus.
- [Joel] Burt Young's
wardrobe by Victoria's Secret.
- [Ingrid] He's awake.
- [Servo] Where'd you come from?
I thought they killed you.
- How you feeling now?
- I feel like a hundred bucks.
- I feel nothing, but I am alive.
- [Fu Manchu] You wish to
remain alive, Professor?
- [Joel] Oh, geez, not him again.
He can suck the air out of any room.
(sighs)
- You will see that he stays
conscious for a few more minutes.
- [Lin Tang] Father, the
attack was successful.
Omar Pasha's men were all destroyed.
- [Servo] Man, your face
could launch a thousand ships.
- And Nayland Smith?
- [Lin Tang] Dead.
This man saw him killed.
- I shall broadcast at midnight.
- [Joel] On the King Biscuit Flower Hour.
- And Heracles?
- He will talk.
You have explained to him,
the information I require from him?
- Yes, of course.
- [Servo] Yes, yes, information, yes.
- Your task is now completed, Dr. Kessler.
- [Servo] These guys.
Come on, dummy.
- And how are we feeling?
- [Joel] Go to bed, old man.
- The formula, Professor.
- No.
- [Servo] Hmm, didn't count on that.
- Castle of Fu Manchu
will be back, after this.
- [Joel] That's enough.
- Huh?
What?
- [Joel] Don't do that
anymore, I'm sick of it.
- [Servo] Welcome to Swing
Back with Jazzbo Collins.
- It's hot in here!
- Then take your clothes off.
- [Joel] Say!
- A gentleman never takes
his clothes off in public!
- [Joel] Well, you're no gentleman,
and we're in private!
- Oh, yes, so we are.
(mumbling)
- [Joel] Fez headed, blah.
(humming)
- Hey, it's Waldo!
They found Waldo, they found Waldo.
- Yes, indeed.
- [Servo] My imitation of a lawnmower.
(coughs)
- [Crow] That was smooth.
(yells)
- [Voiceover] This is my ultimatum.
Within the next few hours --
- [Servo] Hot tomato?
- [Voiceover] The
Bosphorus, and to the city
of Istanbul, will be destroyed.
- It's not true, it can't be true!
- Dr. Petrie --
- Dr. Peepee?
- [Both] Petrie.
- Oh.
- [Joel] Dish.
- [Voiceover] Nayland Smith.
Nayland Smith is dead.
- [Servo] Long live Nayland Smith.
- [Joel] He's dead.
Hey, she reached level three
of Super Mario Brothers.
(humming)
- [Man] Master.
- [Joel] Let me see, what does this say?
I'm bald, bite me, what does that mean?
Wait a minute, after him!
- The formula.
With this, I can control
all things, and all men.
- [Joel] But women, hey,
who can control women?
Are you with me on this, guys, huh?
- Flash the signal.
- [Servo] Not the Fisher flash.
(upbeat pop music)
- [Joel] Hey, it's Spalding Gray,
he's having his perfect moment.
- [Crow] Spalding, man.
You're out too far.
This is supposed to be like a triathlon.
You swim, job, then
appear in a boring movie.
- [Joel] Yeah, well, I'll have
you know that Roger Ebert liked this film.
- I'll have you know, the only thing
Roger Ebert likes is big pans of lasagna.
- [Servo] Lots of them.
Chafe, ooh, chafe ooh.
Ooh, chafe.
Oh, these corduroys.
Oh, chafe, chafe.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, chafe, ooh.
(humming)
(kiss smacks)
- [Kessler] Bad dreams?
- [Crow] You just kissed
the back of my head.
- [Ingrid] The worst dreams
are better than reality.
- [Kessler] Why?
Think that maybe, without
this awful adventure,
we would never have realized
that we were in love.
- [Crow] Now that we're going to die,
I could tell you a
thousand, wonderful hours.
- [Kessler] I didn't see.
- [Ingrid] I didn't want you to see it.
- [Joel] Nobody can see.
- [Ingrid] I didn't want to
distract you from your work,
your experiments, your investigations,
which were all so much
more important than me.
(kiss smack)
- [Servo] You just kissed
me, full on the eyeball.
- [Kessler] You're exactly right, Ingrid.
(spitting)
- I've got hair in my mouth.
- [Servo] Bump!
Ooh, my toe.
Boom!
Oh, my face.
- [Kessler] Thanks to those
many hours of hard work,
during the Professor's operation,
I managed to gain access
to some acid, which I can
now use against Fu Manchu.
- [Servo] Why didn't you do this earlier?
- [Crow] He wanted to
make time with a woman.
- [Servo] Oh.
(explosion)
- [Joel] Tony Blake is The Magician.
Oh, the acid!
Ow, it's stinging.
(suspenseful music)
- [Servo] It looks like
the opening of Mod Squad.
(yells)
Oops!
- [Nayland] Keep quiet!
I shan't hurt you.
I'm from the --
- [Servo] I shall.
- Fu Manchu intends to destroy Istanbul!
- [Servo] What?
- Please!
- [Nayland] Is there a radio transmitter?
- Yes, I can guide you.
Follow me!
- [Lin Tang] Father!
- Are they celebrating Hanukkah?
Dr. Kessler and the
girl, they have escaped.
They have reached the tunnel.
(grunts)
- [Joel] I've been sitting too long.
You know, he looks like Bill Wyman.
- [Crow] He does.
- They will die.
- [Servo] Neat.
- How is Booth?
- [Joel] No.
- [Crow] No?
- [Crow] Oh.
- [Servo] Not with that
Etch A Sketch, you won't.
- We're through!
- [Servo] I don't love you anymore.
- This is Nayland Smith,
speaking from Fu Manchu's headquarters.
Send a warning to the Bosphorus!
- [Servo] Yeah, right.
Come on Mickey Mouse,
broadcasting from Disneyland.
- Nayland Smith.
(explosion)
Come on!
- [Joel] Whoa, getting a little feedback.
Those old tube amps are quirky.
(suspenseful music)
- [Servo] Well, she
gained a little weight.
- [Joel] Mm-hmm.
- Uh-oh, it's after five, the
gateway to eternity's closed!
Yes, yes, dear, I'm doing it, dear.
- Look!
- [Joel] You're wonderful,
I could kiss you.
- [Nayland] This way, through the door!
- [Servo] Remember to keep
left through eternity.
- [Crow] Not that way, that's immortality!
(sniffs)
- [Servo] It's lemon-y Rosco fog.
- I love that stuff.
(sniffs)
Ah.
- The professor.
- [Joel] And Maryann.
- [Nayland] Come on, Professor.
We must get out of here.
- [Servo] Oh, great bedside manner.
- Hey, hey, I'm recovering here.
Get off my bed!
(laughs)
- [Servo] We don't recommend
this for heart patients.
- [Crow] Don't smoke.
Ah, oh!
- [Joel] It's like one of
those old Duran Duran videos.
- He rolls with the punches.
- [Servo] I guess.
- [Joel] Nayland Smith is Mark,
now I'm doing it.
- [Servo] Yep, see?
- [Joel] Oh, this is the worst.
- [Servo] Ah, geez, you still here?
- Don't smoke, don't smoke!
Oh!
- [Servo] Stop it, Crow.
- [Joel] Thank goodness they
found plywood in that cave.
- [Servo] Come along, now.
Time for your sponge bath.
Crotch cam.
Butt cam.
(laughs)
- Come on!
- Keep this scene going!
Stretch it out!
- [Servo] Can't make it.
(grunts)
- [Lin Tang] They have taken Heracles.
- Come!
- [Joel] Mr. Clean, dead at 35.
(groans)
- Oh, yeah, like we believe this.
The gate for immortality
leads to the front yard.
Sure.
- Flood the tunnels.
(suspenseful music)
(moaning)
- [Servo] All of a sudden,
this is like Flashdance.
- [Joel] Sounds like the
water's falling on a piano.
- [Nayland] Don't give up.
- [Servo] Oh, go ahead, and give up.
- Any excuse to get the girl wet.
- [Both] Yep, mm-hmm.
(crying)
- [Crow] By this time,
my lungs were aching.
Oh, who cares?
- [Servo] This is the
trickle down theory of plots.
- So the point of the movie
was to save Burt Young?
- [Servo] I guess so.
- [Joel] Nice halter top.
- [Lisa] I must go back for Omar!
- [Nayland] Come back!
- [Lisa] Omar!
- [Joel] Women, huh?
Can't live with 'em,
can't live without 'em.
I know, I hear ya.
Let's go get some lunch.
- [Servo] Hey, hey, stay off the carpet
with those dirty shoes!
(water splashing)
This is nice.
- The film's in black face now.
Mother!
- [Servo] This is really, really good.
- [Joel] Oh, she's relaxing
in the green room, before the show.
- [Servo] I think I've figured out
what this movie is about, guys.
- [Both] What?
- [Servo] Dry ice, Rosco fog, and blood.
- [Joel] Mm-hmm.
- [Crow] You got it.
Hey, it's a sewer system.
Where's that noise --
- [Servo] Nope, nowhere to be seen.
(yelling)
- [Joel] I didn't quite
catch that, could you repeat?
- [Servo] She said, (yells).
- [Joel] Oh.
(yells)
- [Servo] Guys, I'd say this qualifies
as the Dark Knight of the soul.
- [Crow] Why are we watching this?
- [Servo] What are we, oh.
- Yes, it's Runaway with
the Rich and Famous.
(yells)
- Omar!
- [Servo] Well, I'd say her resentments
for Fu Manchu are all
water under the bridge.
(humming)
- [Joel] Oh, these guys are easy to kill.
They're like mosquitoes,
don't worry about 'em.
- [Crow] Manix.
(humming)
(yells)
- [Servo] We have Paula Abdul's
new video comin' up next on MTV.
(yells)
Yes, you too can relax,
in the new hydro-jet Whirlpool spa.
(thwack)
- [Joel] Classic Captain Kirk chop.
- [Crow] Known as a pork chop.
- [Joel] Giant urinal cakes!
- [Crow] Don't eat 'em.
- [Servo] Screamers.
- Kessler must have got
through, the systems have burst.
- [Servo] Oops.
(explosion)
- [Crow] Let's hide in
the miniature golf course.
- [Servo] MacGuyver!
(rumbling)
- [Joel] Wait, I've got
muffins in the oven.
- [Lin Tang] Father!
- [Joel] You know, if he was
going to express an emotion,
now would be the perfect time to do it.
(laughs)
- [Servo] It's too late.
- [Lin Tang] Father!
(explosion)
- [Servo] Oh, come on!
Things are blowing up that
weren't even in this picture!
- Greece, they just blew up --
- [Servo] Monticello.
- [Crow] Joel, this movie
really isn't very good, is it?
- [Joel] No, it's not.
I'm afraid it's not very good.
- [Servo] The movie sucks, Joel.
It really stinks.
Who's this clown?
- [Voiceover] The world
shall hear from me again.
- [Joel] Come forward, Cowardly Lion!
(cries)
- [Voiceover] The world
shall hear from me again.
- Fu Manchu will be back in
Sweet, Sweet, oh, who cares?
(orchestral string music)
- [Servo] Even the credits stink.
(cries)
I gotta get out of here.
- [Joel] Come on.
(sighs)
- [Crow] I am so depressed.
- Okay, well I....
(crying)
Guess it's time to read a letter.
- Oh, sure, go ahead.
- Like anyone cares.
- Okay, this letter is to Joel, Servo --
- Huzzah.
- And Crow.
- I-key-bach.
- Cambot, you want to put,
oh, what's the use?
(crying)
- Well, we've got 'em
on the run now, Frank.
(laughs)
- I knew you could do it, Dr. F.
- Here's to the evil of Fu Manchu.
- No, to the evil of Fu Man-You.
- Frank, you're the only man in
my organization that'll
talk to me that way.
Put yourself down for honey glazed ham,
and a box of steaks.
- Well, actually, I'm a vegetarian.
(laughs)
Don't know if I told you.
- Nonsense, this is a time to celebrate.
Put yourself down for
two honey glazed hams.
Well, Joely, you and your cyberpunks,
should be ready to admit
defeat right about now.
- You haven't won, Dr. Forrester.
You've lost.
I feel sorry for you.
You're nothing but a sad little man,
in a hole in the ground,
that can only feel
power by hurting others.
- Yeah.
- Well, we've won, because we've survived.
We survived because well,
we're Robinsons, roughly,
and that's what Robinsons
do is survive, basically.
Well, you know what?
If you think it's so easy,
you should give it a try once.
Yeah, you should try to
watch a movie sometime.
- You're beginning to
sound like a Hallmark card.
Tell you what, maybe it's
the Catuaba goin' to my head,
but I'll beat you at my own experiment.
- Heck, we come up with
funnier lines than you guys do.
- Yeah, how hard could it be?
- I mean, you know, in school,
I was something of a class clown.
- Absolutely, let's get this --
- You know, at Arby's,
when I worked there,
I was so funny, my nickname was Zeppo.
- Let's just get the stuff set up, Frank.
Alright?
I should warn you, Joel,
I used to be with the Toastmasters.
I'm somewhat of a rye wit myself.
- [Frank] Ready when you are, CF.
- Ah, right.
Roll 'em, Frank.
- [Frank] Look at that building.
(laughs)
- [Dr. Forrester] It's big.
It's huge.
- [Frank] Here comes a car that
you could say something about.
- [Dr. Forrester] It's
so old, it's an old car.
- [Frank] Yeah, look at it.
Get a load of this lady, she's
gonna get out of that car.
Hi-chee-bah.
- [Dr. Forrester] Yeah,
I was gonna say that.
(laughs)
- [Frank] Well, I said
it first, 'cause you can
make comments about these
things that are happening.
- [Dr. Forrester] Look at her shoes.
- [Frank] Oh, get a load of those things.
- [Dr. Forrester] I'm sure.
I'm walking down the street.
(laughs)
Now, I'm walking down the hallway.
She's, what a dick-weed.
(laughs)
- [Frank] Oh yeah, bite me!
Oh, there's somethings that are really,
that you could make some comments about.
- [Dr. Forrester] You certainly could.
- [Frank] Oh, and she's turning around.
- [Dr. Forrester] Turn it off!
Turn it off!
Well, until next time, crazy Guggenheim.
- You know, we could've
made funny comments,
but the movie wasn't that good.
- Frank!
- [All] Gotcha!
(cheering)
- Frank!
Now, I'm going to have to
put your head in a wood vice.
- Already got it started.
(slow synthesizer music)